<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prologue on</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Prologue on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doc.kerberos.io/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How it works</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/prologue/how/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/prologue/how/</guid><description>When you install Kerberos Open Source or Kerberos Enterprise we will refer to it as the Kerberos Agent. A Kerberos Agent, is a software solution that consist of two pieces: Front-End and Back-End. The Back-End processes the video stream of a single surveillance camera, makes recordings and takes actions (for example sending notifications). The Front-End allows you to review recordings, and configure the Back-End.
A Kerberos agent consists of both a backend en frontend.</description></item><item><title>Deployments</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/prologue/deployments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/prologue/deployments/</guid><description>In this section we will explain some usecases and best practices, which might help you to define the architecture that fits your needs.
Please read the introduction page first, before moving forward.
When starting with Kerberos you might ask yourself, how should I deploy these so called, Kerberos agents? Well, there are different options. You can install a Kerberos agent on a Raspberry Pi, VM, Server or even in a Kubernetes cluster.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/prologue/glossary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/prologue/glossary/</guid><description>While working in the Kerberos Ecosystem, specific words and sentences become to start feel natural. Unfortunately that&amp;rsquo;s not the case for everyone, that&amp;rsquo;s why we added and updated this glossary page, to anyone can come back to this if he would require more detailed explanation.
Agent An agent is a collection of binaries, shipped in different forms such as Docker, Balena, etc). It executes specific tasks related to the camera processing, monitoring, configuration and reviewing.</description></item></channel></rss>