<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prologue on</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Prologue on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/prologue/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/prologue/introduction/</guid><description>The Kerberos(dot)io project, is a video surveillance solution, which was initiated back in 2014. Over the years it has evolved into a trusted, stable and feature-rich video surveillance system. To set the expectations, watch the video below to understand what it can and can&amp;rsquo;t do. If you want to install Kerberos(dot)io, it&amp;rsquo;s recommended to have a look at the architectures page to find the best solution for your usecase.
The name: Kerberos.</description></item><item><title>How it works</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/prologue/how/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/prologue/how/</guid><description>When you install Kerberos Open Source or Kerberos Enterprise we will refer to it as the Kerberos Agent. A Kerberos Agent, is a software solution that consist of two pieces: Front-End and Back-End. The Back-End processes the video stream of a single surveillance camera, makes recordings and takes actions (for example sending notifications). The Front-End allows you to review recordings, and configure the Back-End.
A Kerberos agent consists of both a backend en frontend.</description></item><item><title>Deployments</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/prologue/deployments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/prologue/deployments/</guid><description>In this section we will explain some usecases and best practices, which might help you to define the architecture that fits your needs.
Please read the introduction page first, before moving forward.
When starting with Kerberos you might ask yourself, how should I deploy these so called, Kerberos agents? Well, there are different options. You can install a Kerberos agent on a Raspberry Pi, VM, Server or even in a Kubernetes cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>