<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enterprise on</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/</link><description>Recent content in Enterprise on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First things first</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/first-things-first/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/first-things-first/</guid><description>Kerberos Opensource and Kerberos Enterprise both store recordings on the local disk. To centralise your data at a single place, additional solutions are available.
Kerberos Hub One or more Kerberos Enterprise agents, can store their data directly on Kerberos Hub, and benefit from the visualisation layer Kerberos Hub offers. When doing this your recordings will be uploaded inside the Kerberos datacenter (which is a black box for you).
Kerberos Vault In addition to that you have the option to Bring Your Own Storage (BYOS), using Kerberos Vault.</description></item><item><title>Get Started</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/get-started/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/get-started/</guid><description>Once you&amp;rsquo;ve installed Kerberos Storage, you will have the Kerberos Storage web app running. This web app allows you to administrate Kerberos Storage. You can add storage providers, queues, accounts, and more from a single interface. Isn&amp;rsquo;t that great.
Despite exposing a web app, Kerberos Storage also ships with a number of API&amp;rsquo;s. These API&amp;rsquo;s are exposed as, Swagger documentation, and can be used for extension and integration usecases. Think about following usecase.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/installation/</guid><description>Kerberos Open Source (v3) is the next generation of Kerberos.io, and is the successor of (v1/v2). More specifically it will replace and merge the machinery and web repositories. A switch in technologies and architecture has been made. Version 3 is still under active development, and not yet released. The progress can be followed at the develop branch and project overview.
What is changing? At the bottom line, we are rebuilding the project from scratch using a different technology stack.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Installation</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/installation-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/installation-cloud/</guid><description>If not already the case, start by installing a Kubernetes cluster. This can be done on one of the hyperscalers (AWS, GCP or Azure), cloud providers (Digital Ocean, Scaleway, etc) or on-premise in your own private network.
Prerequisites Kerberos Storage is the storage component for Kerberos Enterprise. It is used to store your recordings at a central place, in the storage system you prefer. Next to that it can be used for extension and integration capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Edge Installation</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/installation-edge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/installation-edge/</guid><description>Welcome to the Kerberos Storage Edge installation. This is the way to go if you want to install Kerberos Storage on your Baremetal infrastructure or inside your Private Cloud.
Before we can actual start installing the different deployments in our cluster, we need to make sure we have one available.
Prerequisites Kerberos Storage is the storage component for Kerberos Enterprise. It is used to store your recordings at a central place, in the storage system you prefer.</description></item><item><title>Providers</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/providers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/providers/</guid><description>Kerberos Storage allows you to attach one or more (and different) storage providers. These providers could be in the cloud like S3, Google Cloud Storage or Azure blob storage, or providers on premise such as Minio.
Depending on your use case: Kerberos Storage Cloud or Kerberos Storage Edge, you will opt for a specific storage provider. For example in the case Kerberos Storage Edge, it makes sense to store your recordings also at the edge.</description></item><item><title>Recycle</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/recycle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/recycle/</guid><description>Next to storing your recordings, recycling up is also important. You have to avoid your disk being filled up and locking up the entire system and cluster, or you simply have to reduce cost. To make this possible we offer a recycle service called Kerberos Storage Recycle, which you can use to remove recordings based on different rules.
Recycling rules Different recycling rules can be configured in the Kerberos Storage app.</description></item><item><title>Releases</title><link>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/releases/releases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.doc.kerberos.live/vault/releases/releases/</guid><description>A license can be obtained by requesting a contract offert a cedric@verstraeten.io. Once agreed, a license will be generated on the Kerberos License server.
EULA This agreement (or “EULA”) is a legal agreement between the person, company or organization (“You”) that has licensed a software product (Kerberos Storage) and Verstraeten.io (“Licensor” or “Application Provider”). The Product is to be obtained only through Docker Hub (https://hub.docker.com), and by obtaining a purchased license.</description></item></channel></rss>