<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Opensource on</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/</link><description>Recent content in Opensource on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First things first</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/first-things-first/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/first-things-first/</guid><description>Kerberos started as an Open Source project back in 2014. Our main goal was, and still is, to provide everyone in this world with a free, professional and complete video surveillance system, which they can install in a couple of minutes. Kerberos was initially developed for the Raspberry Pi, due to this many of the tools we have been using are lightweight and fast (such as C++). Over the years we have found other ways to make Kerberos available, such as KiOS (our custom Linux), Docker and Kubernetes.</description></item><item><title>Get started</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/get-started/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/get-started/</guid><description>Once you&amp;rsquo;ve installed Kerberos Open Source, you will have access to the web application. This web application allows you to administrate the machinery.
Welcome page The first time you open a browser, and navigate to the web application (ip address of your device), you will land on the welcome page. This page will guide you through some basic steps and set simple configurations such as username and password.
The landing page after successfully installing Kerberos Opensource.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/installation/</guid><description>Kerberos Open Source comes with different installation flavours. So you might think, why? The reason is simple, depending on the use case one option is better than another. A short list of recommendations:
Plug and play KiOS: You have a Raspberry Pi, and you only want to run a Kerberos agent on it. Docker: You have a lot of IP cameras, and/or don&amp;rsquo;t want to mess with dependencies. Balena: Runnning the Kerberos Docker container on top of Balena.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Installation</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/installation-advanced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/installation-advanced/</guid><description>Following installation methods are only for advanced users, who need to have more control over the Kerberos Open Source environment.
Raspbian If you have already an OS (e.g. Raspbian Buster) flashed to your Raspberry Pi, then it makes sense to install the Kerberos agent on top of your existing OS. There are two ways to achieve this:
Install the Kerberos agent using Docker (more info below), or you can install the Kerberos agent manually (machinery + web).</description></item><item><title>Release notes</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/releases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/releases/</guid><description>2.8.0 Aligned machinery, web and KiOS versions. Too many people were confused by the versioning.
Web Videos displayed on canvas were blocked in latest browsers. Disabled reboot and shutdown. Disabled upgrade process, use fwupdate shell command instead. KiOS Major upgrade, solved many different problems (list to long); not possible to upgrade from 2.7.0 to 2.8.0. Updated firmware to latest Raspbian (raspberrypi-kernel_1.20180417-1). Support for the Raspberry Pi 4. 2.</description></item><item><title>License</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/license/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/license/</guid><description>Summary You are free to:
Share — copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format Adapt — remix, transform, and build upon the material The license Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International Public License By exercising the Licensed Rights (defined below), You accept and agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International Public License (&amp;ldquo;Public License&amp;rdquo;). To the extent this Public License may be interpreted as a contract, You are granted the Licensed Rights in consideration of Your acceptance of these terms and conditions, and the Licensor grants You such rights in consideration of benefits the Licensor receives from making the Licensed Material available under these terms and conditions.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/upgrade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/upgrade/</guid><description>To upgrade your Kerberos agent to a new version you should follow the approach which fits your initial installation method. If you installed KiOS follow the KiOS upgrade procedure, if installed on Raspbian follow the Raspbian upgrade procedure, etc.
Please note that it might be possible that some new files are added or existing files were updated. To make sure everything works as expected, you should clear your browser cache.</description></item><item><title>Contribute</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/contribute/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/contribute/</guid><description>In this document we describe the different things you need to know if you would like to add a new feature to Kerberos Open Source, or change some of its behaviour for your own use case.
Before starting, as you might have read already, you need to know that Kerberos Open Source consists of two solutions. A front-end, also called web, which allows you to review the recordings and to configure the back-end settings.</description></item><item><title>Machinery</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/machinery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/machinery/</guid><description>The machinery is the processing engine of Kerberos Open Source. It&amp;rsquo;s an image processing framework, written in C++, who benefits from other third party libraries (OpenCV, etc). It takes images from the type of camera (USB-, IP- or RPi-camera) you&amp;rsquo;ve configured in the configuration files and executes one ore more algorithms and post-processes (e.g. save a snapshot). The configuration files allow you to define the type of camera, post-processes, conditions and much more; it&amp;rsquo;s highly configurable.</description></item><item><title>Web</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/web/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/opensource/web/</guid><description>The web is responsible for the visualization. It&amp;rsquo;s a GUI which helps the user to find activity at a specific period, configure the machinery, view a live stream, see system information and much more.
It&amp;rsquo;s written in PHP using the extremely popular PHP Framework Laravel, and Javascript using the client-side framework BackboneJS. We will discuss the different pages and functionality briefly. Please check out the demo environment if you want to see a real life example.</description></item></channel></rss>