<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enterprise on</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/</link><description>Recent content in Enterprise on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First things first</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/first-things-first/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/first-things-first/</guid><description>Over the years Kerberos evolved into a mature and stable solution. Lots of people and companies started to adopt the system, and requested enhancements. Despite the fact that Kerberos Open Source is stable and feature rich, every solution has its limitations, especially if you aim to scale it.
That being said, Kerberos Open Source is perfect when monitoring a limited set of surveillance cameras, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t scale well if you plan to monitor dozens or hundreds of surveillance cameras.</description></item><item><title>Get Started</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/get-started/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/get-started/</guid><description>Once you&amp;rsquo;ve installed Kerberos Enterprise, you will have the Kerberos Enterprise Factory webapp running inside your cluster. This web application allows you to administrate your Kerberos Enterprise agents as deployments/pods. It comes a bunch of other features as well, read on.
Important to note is that this web app is relying on the Golang Kubernetes SDK, so that means from an administration point of view, you could simply use the well known kubectl command.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/installation/</guid><description>Kerberos Enterprise can be installed where Kubernetes can be installed. This means that it can run at the Edge - Baremetal -, in the cloud - VMs - or at Kubernetes service providers - SAAS - such as GCP, Azure, AWS, DigitalOcean, and the list goes on.
Although you might except Kubernetes at the Edge or Kubernetes in the cloud, there are no differences, well sorry to say there are. As Kubernetes service providers implemented features such as LoadBalancers, Persistent Volumes, and others, they have automated and integrated a huge portion of the Kubernetes stack with their related PAAS services.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Installation</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/installation-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/installation-cloud/</guid><description>Start by installing a Kubernetes cluster. This can be done on one of the hyperscalers (AWS, GCP or Azure), cloud providers (Digital Ocean, Scaleway, etc) or on-premise in your own private network.
Installation Before setting up Kerberos Enterprise, some configuration needs to happen. First thing that we need to do is setting up the RBAC permissions (Role Based Access Control). We need to enable this to be able to query specific endpoints from the Kubernetes API.</description></item><item><title>Edge Installation</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/installation-edge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/installation-edge/</guid><description>Welcome to the Kerberos Enterprise Edge installation. This is the way to go if you want to install Kerberos Enterprise on your Baremetal infrastructure or inside your Private Cloud.
When you start having bigger deployments it&amp;rsquo;s recommended to go with a Kubernetes approach.
Before we can actual start installing the different deployments in our cluster, we need to make sure we have one available.
Prerequisites Docker If you have a fresh Linux installation, make sure you have Docker installed.</description></item><item><title>Releases</title><link>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/releases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doc.kerberos.io/enterprise/releases/</guid><description>1.0.0 Factory React application using the Kubernetes and Docker Golang SDK. Possibility to add deployments one by one or in bulk (Excel). Configure machinery deployments: select a region of interest, specify recording time (pre, andd post recording), specify time interval. Global configuration page, where you specify your cloud credentials at a single place.</description></item></channel></rss>